http://www.appleinteriors.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Who we are
Our website address is: http://www.appleinteriors.co.uk.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymised string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Contact forms
There are no contact forms on this website.
Cookies
This site uses cookies to enhance your browsing experience, no personal data is collected by the site. By accepting the cookie notice you are giving permission for the site to write a cookie on your machine, you can delete this at any time.
Analytics
This site uses Google Analytics to track user numbers, the only personal information collected is the IP address. By accepting the cookie notice you are giving permission for this data to be tracked.
Who we share your data with
We do not collect or share and personal data for marketing purposes.
Your contact information
If you have any concerns regarding the use of your data please contact Apple Interiors at sales@appleinteriors.co.uk.
MenuPROJECT MANAGEMENT
REFURBISHMENT
BAR AND RECEPTION COUNTERS
HOTEL BEDROOM FURNITURE
LATEST NEWS
CONTACT APPLE
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.OkNoPrivacy policy
